

About me

Software engineer with 3 years of experience in developing and managing custom software solutions. Solid skills in Javascript, Typescript, PHP, Python and agile methodologies. Highly assertive and passionate about continuous learning and tackling complex challenges with creative and analytical approaches.

Contact



+58 424-6733416



luis06jose@gmail.com



luis-medina-app.vercel.app



www.linkedin.com/in/luisjose-medina-sandoval-444262195/

Tools

- Office: Excel (advanced),
 Word, Access (basic).
- Project Management: Jira, ClickUp, SCRUM.
- Code Management: Git, GitHub, NodeJS, Composer.

Luis José Medina S.

Software Developer

Work experience

Front-end Web Development

SysModelers | August 2021 - February 2022

- Development of user-centered and accessible UI/UX experiences utilizing React components and CoreUI libraries.

Quote Manager for Excel

Corretaje de Seguros ASECA | July 2021 - May 2024

- Developed and managed a suite of customized Excel-based quote systems for international, national, and regional insurances.

Full-stack Web Development

Romano's Pizza | July 2021 - November 2022

- Web point-of-sale application project developed using a custom PHP framework, MySQL, Vue.js and Vuetify.

Manager of Network Department

Regalado Group: Bienes Raices | March 2022 - September 2023

- Responsible for real estate property management, commercial website administration and content management with Joomla CMS.

Full-stack Web Development

Universidad Rafael Belloso Chacín | January 2024 - April 2024

- Senior Thesis Project - Responsive crowdfunding web application developed using the FastAPI (Python) framework, React and Bootstrap.

Full-stack Web Development

Sabe de Seguros | January 2024 - May 2024

- Project development for several responsive web quote systems for the company website using a custom WordPress plugin with PHP, MySQL, Vue and Vuetify.
- Content management on the website using WordPress as the CMS.

Education

Universidad Rafael Belloso Chacín

Graduated in Computer Engineering | April 2024

Skills

- Languages: Javascript,
 Typescript, PHP, Python, C#,
 Java, C++.
- Web: HTML, TailwindCSS, CSS, Bootstrap, Vuetify.
- Frameworks: Vue.js, React, Next.js, Laravel, FastAPI.
- DB: MySQL, PosgreSQL.

Languages

Spanish:

Native.

English:

Basic.